{"quiz2" :[
  {
    "id" : 1,
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Java is an Interpreted Language",
    "correctAnswer" : "false",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
 {     "id" : 2,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What is <h1>?",
    "correctAnswer" : "first heading",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
   {  
    "id" : 3,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What transmits between two computers?",
    "correctAnswer" : "network",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {
    "id" : 4,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Coaxial cables protect from interference",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 5,   
   "questionType": "checkBox",
      "questionText": "Which are used in HTML?",
      "correctAnswer": ["<p>","<h2>"],
    "options" : ["<p>","<h2>","int", "import"]
  }, {  
    "id" : 6,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What sends a network request?",
    "correctAnswer" : "HTTP",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {
    "id" : 7,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "There are 7 layers to a network",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 8,   
   "questionType": "checkBox",
      "questionText": "Which are cyberattacks?",
      "correctAnswer": ["worm","DNS Overloading"],
    "options" : ["worm","DNS Overloading","computer homicide", "not buying a computer"]
  }, {"id" : 9,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What is a list tag?",
    "correctAnswer" : "<li>",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {
    "id" : 10,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "A trojan horse is  cyberattack",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 11,   
   "questionType": "checkBox",
      "questionText": "Which are functions in html?",
      "correctAnswer": ["asynch","arrow functions"],
    "options" : ["asynch","arrow functions","json objects", "arrays"]
},{"id" : 12,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What does CSS handle?",
    "correctAnswer" : "the styling of an HTML page",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {
    "id" : 13,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "CSS can modify images",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 14,   
   "questionType": "checkBox",
      "questionText": "Which are specific examples of what CSS handles?",
      "correctAnswer": ["padding","borders"],
    "options" : ["padding","borders","json objects", "arrays"]
  },{"id" : 15,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "How do you insert data from another location in HTML?",
    "correctAnswer" : "send a request of information to the server",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {
    "id" : 16,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Arrays can only be 2d",
    "correctAnswer" : "false",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 17,   
   "questionType": "checkBox",
      "questionText": "Which of the following are used in SQL?",
      "correctAnswer": ["Select","OrderBY"],
    "options" : ["Select","OrderBY","json objects", "arrays"]
  },
  {"id" : 18,   
   "questionType" : "text_input",
    "questionText" : "What class do you import in Java to get random numbers?",
    "correctAnswer" : "java.util.Random",
    "answerFieldId" : "answer_to_question"
  },
  {
    "id" : 19,   
   "questionType" : "true_false",
    "questionText" : "Arrays can hold instatiates of objects",
    "correctAnswer" : "true",
    "options" : ["true", "false"]
  },
  {
    "id" : 20,   
   "questionType": "checkBox",
      "questionText": "Which of the following are job in the CS field?",
      "correctAnswer": ["All of the above"],
    "options" : ["Programmer","software developer","Systems Analyst", "All of the above"]
  },
  
]
  
}
